Yonatan Erez - CV

Tel Aviv

050-6569632

jontaner12@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/yonatan-erez2904

Github: https://github.com/Yoniere

Summary

Full-Stack / Frontend Web Developer, passionate about solving challenges, with experience in writing single-page-applications using the latest WEB technologies such as Node.js, Vue.js, Vuex, React, Redux. Additional tech skills: MongoDB, MySQL, JavaScript(ES6), HTML5, CSS3,SASS, GIT, GitHub.

Experience

"CODING ACADEMY" BOOTCAMP FINAL PROJECT - AIRYNY | 2022

- Vacation rental marketplace inspired by Airbnb.com & is built as a 3 team effort: https://protected-reaches-97996.herokuapp.com/#/
- · MVC Frameworks, Single-Page-Applications using Vue.js, Vuex.
- · Server-side programming, APIs and REST with Node.js, MongoDB.
- · Modern JavaScript (ES6), HTML5, CSS3 and SASS.
- Responsibilities: details component, connecting server side, pixel perfect, responsive design, order process and more...

PRODUCT MANAGER | LG ELECTRONICS | 2017-2021

- · Fluent work in English.
- Setting KPI goals (revenue, market share, strategic products, and brand awareness).
- · Formulate and implement business strategy in order to increase revenue and profitability.
- · 2019 Best Employee of the Year & 2020 Middle East and Africa Best Employee of the Year.

ACCOUNT MANAGER | FLYING CARGO | 2015-2017

· Critical shipping, temperature control shipping, problem resolution according to clients demands.

Education

Full-Stack developer - Coding Academy | 2022

· An intensive coding bootcamp (640 hours)

BSC | Industrial Engineering and Management specialized in Information Systems

2012-2016 - SHENKAR SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING & DESIGN

Military Service

2007-2010 | COMMANDER AT THE ARTILLERY CORPS

· commander of a team of fighters, in charge of an armored personal carrier.